<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WillowHealth</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_insights">Insights</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_name">Name</string>
    <string  name = "question_sleep_time">How many hours did you sleep?</string>
    <string  name = "initial_gpt_message">Welcome to our Willow Health Assistant!
        Our chatbot is here to assist you in analyzing and improving your health habits.
        Whether you are looking to optimize your sleep patterns or track your daily steps,
        our chatbot is designed to provide you with personalized insights and guidance.
        Simply engage with our chatbot to start your journey towards better health and well-being.
        Let is work together to achieve your health goals!</string>
    <string name="intro_survey_message"> I am writing to seek your expertise in analyzing the sleep quality data of the respondent mentioned above.
        The provided survey data covers a week-long period and includes various metrics related to their sleep patterns and subjective experiences.
        Analysis Request:
        Could you please analyze the trends and patterns observed in the respondent\'s sleep data over the past week?
        Identify any potential issues or areas for improvement based on the data provided.
        Offer insights into factors that may be contributing to any observed sleep disturbances or poor sleep quality.
        Provide personalized advice or recommendations to help the respondent improve their sleep quality and overall well-being.
        User request (can be empty): %s
        Survey Data:
    </string>
    <string name="sleep_title">Sleep</string>
    <string name="steps_title">Steps</string>
    <string name="calories_title">Calories</string>
    <string name="sleep_duration">Sleep</string>
    <string name="calories">Calories</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="sleep_duration_title">Sleep Duration</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="account_circle">Account circle</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="woke_up_frequently">Woke up frequently</string>
    <string name="had_difficulty_falling_asleep">Had difficulty falling asleep</string>
    <string name="experienced_nightmares">Experienced nightmares</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>

</resources>